Guide to the University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.) University Relations Records 1930-2012
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Biographical Information, 1937-1983; Series III
  - Patzig, William D., 1978; affiliation: AFIT Program (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/94)
  - Paul, David, ca. 1960s; affiliation: Visiting Professor English (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/95)
  - Pease, Laurel E., 1969-1971; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/96)
  - Pedersen, Clifford Wayne, 1967-1970; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/97)
  - Perry, Laurence, 1961-1972; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/98)
  - Petersham, Misha, 1973, 1975; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/99)
  - Peterson, Brent, 1971-1972; affiliation: Speech Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/100)
  - Persterson, Donald W., 1967; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/101)
  - Peterson, James A. Dr., 1965-1975; affiliation: Geology (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/102)
  - Peterson, John A., 1955-1973; affiliation: Mathematics and Computer Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/103)
  - Petrusewicz, Kazimierz Dr., 1967; affiliation: Senior Foreign Science Fellow (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/104)
  - Pettit, Lawrence K., 1975-1976; affiliation: Commissioner Higher Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/105)
  - Pfister, Robert D., undated; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/106)
  - Phillips, Elizabeth, 1972-1973; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/107)
  - Phillips, Thomas P. SGT., 1964, 1967; affiliation: ROTC (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/108)
  - Piane, Berta, 1975; affiliation: UM Center for Student Development (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/109)
  - Piercy, Marge, ca. 1978; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/110)
  - Pilote, Bob, 1979; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/111)
  - Pirron, Dr. Gordon D., 1973-1975; affiliation: Accounting and Finance (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/112)
  - Pope, Allen L Dr., 1967-1969; affiliation: Director, Indian Training (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/113)
  - Pope, Jack M., 1973; affiliation: UM Order of the Grizzly Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/114)
  - Pope, Dr. Shirley A., 1975; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/115)
  - Pope, Walter L., 1947, 1966; affiliation: Law, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/116)
  - Postle, Robert, 1981; affiliation: Botany (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/117)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1968; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/118)
  - Puckett, Howard, 1973-1975; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/119)
  - Pugh, Karen G., 1973; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/120)
  - Pulley, Barbara Elaine Walikonis, 1969, 1973; affiliation: Accountant (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/121)
  - Purdy, Cinda, 1975-1977; affiliation: Center for Continuing Education and Summer Programs (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/122)
  - Rabold, Sue, 1975-1977; affiliation: Montana Public Employees Association UM Chapter (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/123)
  - Radner, Benjamin J. Dr., 1946-1962; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/124)
  - Randak, Coburn Reed, ca. 1972; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/1)
  - Rawdon, John C., 1971; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/2)
  - Rea, Dean, 1963-1966; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/3)
  - Redwolf, Rosella, 1971; affiliation: Native American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/4)
  - Reimer, Milton K. Dr., 1969-1973; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/5)
  - Reston, James, 1977; affiliation: Mansfield Lecture Series, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/6)
  - Reynolds, Jeff, 1975; affiliation: University Center Judo (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/7)
  - Rhinehart, Nasby, 1956-1979; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/8)
  - Richards, Dennis Lee, 1968-1973; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/9)
  - Riese, haran Clifford, 1960-1976; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/10)
  - Riordan, George, 1975-1977; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/11)
  - Rittenour, Clifford H., 1966; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/12)
  - Roberts, Janet C., 1970-1975; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/13)
  - Roberts, Raynor H., 1970-1971; affiliation: Extension and Continuing Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/14)
  - Roberts, Wallace, 1974-1977; affiliation: Physical Plant (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/15)
  - Robertson, James I. Jr. Dr., 1966-1967; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/16)
  - Robinson, Daniel W., 1976; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/17)
  - Rocheleau, Louis A., 1968-1971; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/18)
  - Rockwell, Nancy L., 1975; affiliation: Administrative Assistant- Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/19)
  - Rogers, Nancy K., ca. 1970; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/20)
  - Roggensack, Delinda, ca. 1970; affiliation: Music Education visiting professor (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/21)
  - Romeo, William, 1976-1977; affiliation: CSD counseling psychologist (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/22)
  - Rowan, W.B. Dr., 1963-1966; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/23)
  - Rudegeair, Thomas, 1976; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/24)
  - Rulffes, Walter O., 1967; affiliation: Assistant Director Food Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/25)
  - Rummel, J. Francis Dr., 1967-1976; affiliation: Dean of Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/26)
  - Runberg, Marie, 1967; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/27)
  - Russ, Ed, 1967; affiliation: Chief of University Police (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/28)
  - Rustberggard, Birger, 1974-1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/29)
  - Rustvold, Herbert, 1972-1973; affiliation: Chef- Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/30)
  - Ryan, Jack, 1958-1967; affiliation: Executive Director Alumni Association (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/31)
  - Sakai,Yoshio, 1976-1977; affiliation: Guest Faculty (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/32)
  - Sale, Dennis, 1967-1975; affiliation: UM Office of Information Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/33)
  - Sanghi, Dr. Ajay K., 1975; affiliation: Business (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/34)
  - Sappenfield, Bert R., 1953-1971; affiliation: Psychology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/35)
  - Scerbo, Barry, 1972; affiliation: Food Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/36)
  - Schaefer, Hugh, 1972-1976; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/37)
  - Schaill, Malinda, 1974-1975; affiliation: Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/38)
  - Schmidt, Wyman, 1973; affiliation: Inter-mountain Forest and Range Experiment Station's Forestry Sciences Laboratory (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/39)
  - Schodt, Eddie William Dr., 1967-1968; affiliation: Political Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/40)
  - Schoelzel, Stephanie A., 1971-1976; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/41)
  - Schoenberger, Nancy J., 1977; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/42)
  - Schneider, Joanne, ca. 1978; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/43)
  - Schroeber, Anita, 1969; affiliation: Sentinel Yearbook Editor (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/44)
  - Schultz, John D., 1976; affiliation: Associate Dean of the School of Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/45)
  - Schultz, Phillip Dr., ca. late 1960s; affiliation: Mathematics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/46)
  - Schwanke, Dale, 1977; affiliation: Young Alumni Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/47)
  - Scwanke, William R., 1967; affiliation: Information Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/48)
  - Schwartz, Howard, 1975; affiliation: Bureau of Government Research Coordinator (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/49)
  - Schwartz, James R., 1971; affiliation: Accounting and Finance (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/50)
  - Schwendiman, Carl J., 1974-1975; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/51)
  - Scott, Sally J., 1973-1974; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/52)
  - Seedort, Evelyn H., 1956; affiliation: Speech (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/53)
  - Seifert, William F., ca. 1971; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/54)
  - Seino, Alan, 1972-1973; affiliation: Student Personnel Manager (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/55)
  - Selke, George A., 1948-1950; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/56)
  - Sepanski, Stephen J., 1973; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/57)
  - Serba, Walter, 1976; affiliation: Athletics- Equipment Manager (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/58)
  - Serha, Liza, 1977; affiliation: Friends of the University Library (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/59)
  - Serrette, Ralph, 1973-1974; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/60)
  - Shandorf, Frank S., 1969, 1974; affiliation: Physical Plant (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/61)
  - Shannon, Pat, 1972; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/62)
  - Shapowaloff, Lubrov Mrs. Dr., 1971-1976; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/63)
  - Shavzin, Alan, ca. 1970; affiliation: Philosophy (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/64)
  - Shepherd, William C., 1974-1982; affiliation: Religious Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/65)
  - Sheppard, Dr. Douglas C., 1958-1964; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/66)
  - Sherman, John W., undated; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/67)
  - Schideler, Lee Elizabeth, 1972; affiliation: Clinical Audiologist, Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/68)
  - Sievers, Joanne Lester, 1974; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/69)
  - Silvernail, David H., 1971; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/70)
  - Simmons, Lee H., 1969; affiliation: Assistant to President Pantzer (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/71)
  - Simpson, Joanne, 1974; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/72)
  - Singer, George Dr., 1966-1967; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/73)
  - Sletten, Vernon O., 1954-1967; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/74)
  - Slocum, Sally V., 1975-1976; affiliation: Anthropology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/75)
  - Smirnoff, Patricia, 1967; affiliation: Information Services- Coordinator of Events (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/76)
  - Smith, David C., 1976-1978; affiliation: Dean of Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/77)
  - Smith, David J. Dr., 1966-1968; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/78)
  - Smith, Gary, 1975; affiliation: "Dance Montana" Business Manager (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/79)
  - Smith, Harold L., ca. 1971; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/80)
  - Smith, Joan (Dr.), 1966; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/81)
  - Smith, John, 1976-1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/82)
  - Smith, Leo, 1959-1972; affiliation: Registrar (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/83)
  - Smith, Peter B. Jr. Dr., ca. 1970s; affiliation: Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/84)
  - Smith, Richard L., 1970-1974; affiliation: African American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/85)
  - Smith, Robert L., 1969, 1971; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/86)
  - Smith, Russell E., 1977; affiliation: Law Endowment Fund (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/87)
  - Smith, Stephen Sowell, ca. 1970; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/88)
  - Smith, Thomas E., ca. 1970; affiliation: Accounting and Finance (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/89)
  - Smith, William W., 1973; affiliation: UM Computer Center (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/90)
  - Smoyer, Franklin R., ca. 1972; affiliation: Management (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/91)
  - Snow, Dr. Vernon P., 1960-1966; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/92)
  - Sogandares, Franklin Dr., 1971-1972; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/93)
  - Sorensen, Chester A., 1963; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/94)
  - Sorenson, Thora Dr., 1947-1956; affiliation: Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/95)
  - South, Garry Dean, 1973; affiliation: ASUM President (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/96)
  - Sowerwine, Lucille Hardy, 1971; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/97)
  - Spang, Alonzo T. Sr., 1970-1971; affiliation: Native American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/98)
  - Speake, Constance J., 1971-1979; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/99)
  - Spartano, Phillip James, 1971; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/100)
  - Sperry, Edward, 1972-1975; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/101)
  - Springsteel, Fred N., 1974-1975; affiliation: Math (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/102)
  - Srivastava, Hart Mohan, ca. 1970; affiliation: Math (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/103)
  - Staael, Nora, 1969-1976; affiliation: Physical Therapy (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/104)
  - Stade, George Dr., undated; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/105)
  - Stafford, Dr. Harry C., 1976; affiliation: Religious Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/106)
  - Starkey, Steve, 1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/107)
  - Stark, Heman G., 1962; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/108)
  - Starzynski, Charles, 1975; affiliation: Publicity Director- Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/109)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1948; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/110)
  - Steadman, R., 1969; affiliation: Unknown (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/111)
  - Steele, James L., ca. 1972; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/112)
  - Steele, Thomas J., ca. 1971; affiliation: AFIT Program (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/113)
  - Steele, Robert W., 1956-1981; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/114)
  - Stefanich, Gregory Paul, ca. 1970; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/115)
  - Sterling, Carol De George, 1971; affiliation: Assistant Director- Residence Halls (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/116)
  - Stevens, Reid Elliot, ca. 1970; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/117)
  - Stewart, Gertrude H., 1957; affiliation: Assistant to Director of Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/118)
  - Stewart, Ray, 1967; affiliation: Forestry Editor (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/119)
  - Stinnes, Manfred H., ca. 1972; affiliation: Political Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/120)
  - Stockburger, Thomas A., 1974-1975; affiliation: ASUM (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/121)
  - Stocking, J.R., 1967-1969; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/122)
  - Stockstad, Dwight S., ca. late 1960s; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/123)
  - Stoodley, Agnes L. Dr., 1947-1970; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/124)
  - Stroh, Gordon Vernon, 1969; affiliation: Foundation Accountant (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/125)
  - Sullivan, Joe, 1970; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/126)
  - Sullivan, Robert E., 1971-1979; affiliation: Dean of Law School (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/127)
  - Sullivan, Robert E., 1963-1974; affiliation: Dean of Law School (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/128)
  - Sun, Li-the, ca. 1970; affiliation: Business and Economic Research (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/129)
  - Susott, Ronald A., 1972-1974; affiliation: Forestry and Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/130)
  - Swan, Robert J., 1973-1974; affiliation: Native American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/131)
  - Swanson, Margaret A., 1970-1976; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 5/132)
  - Swanson, Max Randolph, 1967; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/1)
  - Swarthout, Jack, 1973-1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/2)
  - Swarthout, Jack, 1968-1973; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/3)
  - Swartz, Billie Anne McFadden, 1967; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/4)
  - Swayze, Col. Jack, 1969-1972; affiliation: Aerospace Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/5)
  - Swearingen, T.G., 1956-1960; affiliation: Maintenance Engineer (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/6)
  - Sykes, Earl F., 1962, 1976; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/7)
  - Taber, Richard D. Dr., 1956-1968; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/8)
  - Tafoya, Dr. Estelle, 1977; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/9)
  - Taillon, Gregory J., 1979; affiliation: AFIT Program (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/10)
  - Talbot, James L. Dr., 1971-1976; affiliation: Geology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/11)
  - Tanner, Dr. William, 1975-1976; affiliation: African American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/12)
  - Tascher, Harold Dr., 1954-1970; affiliation: Social Welfare (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/13)
  - Taskey, Ronald, 1972; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/14)
  - Tatsuyama, Toshimi Dr., 1958-1967; affiliation: Religion (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/15)
  - Taybi, Abderrahmane, 1973; affiliation: Mudd, John (Law) (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/16)
  - Taylor, Calvin W. Dr., 1966; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/17)
  - Taylor, Carmen C., Ca. 1971; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/18)
  - Taylor, Maurice, 1966-1968; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/19)
  - Taylor, Norman E., 1965-1976; affiliation: Administrative Vice President (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/20)
  - Taylor, William J., 1968-1970; affiliation: University of Montana Treasurer (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/21)
  - Templeton, James R. Dr., 1964-1973; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/22)
  - Thane, Jeremy G., ca. 1955; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/23)
  - Thieme, Fred, 1966; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/24)
  - Thomas, Beverly Jane, 1967-1968; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/25)
  - Thomas- Rupert, Diane, 1977; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/26)
  - Thompson, Ronald, ca. 1968; affiliation: Sociology and Social Welfare (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/27)
  - Thomson, Frederick Wayne, 1971-1972; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/28)
  - Thrasher, James M. Dr., 1964-1967; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/29)
  - Tickell, Lee J., 1968-1970; affiliation: Student Union Program Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/30)
  - Tiddy, Suzanne G., 1973; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/31)
  - Todd, Regina, ca. 1965; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/32)
  - Tollefesen, Christine L., 1973-1974; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/33)
  - Tolliver, Rosalind Mullen, 1967; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/34)
  - Tomlinson, Dale, 1975-1978; affiliation: V.P. Fiscal Affairs (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/35)
  - Toole, John, 1975; affiliation: V.P. Constitutional Convention (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/36)
  - Toplarski, Lois Marie, 1967; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/37)
  - Torgrimson, Herb, 1973-1977; affiliation: Physical Plant (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/38)
  - Tourangeau, Phillip, 1970-1975; affiliation: Environmental Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/39)
  - Tpuzeau, Roy F., 1979; affiliation: Computer Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/40)
  - Townsend, John, 1972-1973; affiliation: Anthropology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/41)
  - Townsend, John M., ca. 1972; affiliation: Anthropology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/42)
  - Traber, Fred W., 1971; affiliation: UM Student Ambassador (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/43)
  - Trask, Marvin W., 1967; affiliation: Mathematics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/44)
  - Tuchman, Barbara, 1978; affiliation: Mansfield Lecture Series, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/45)
  - Tunnell, Gary G., 1973-1974; affiliation: Anthropology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/46)
  - Turner, John, 1975; affiliation: Religious Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/47)
  - Turner, Robert T. Dr., 1947-1972; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/48)
  - Uda, Lowell Masato, ca. 1970; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/49)
  - Valach, Anthrony, 1966-1968; affiliation: Student Union Program Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/50)
  - Van De Wetering, John E. Dr., 1961-1976; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/51)
  - Van Duser, Cyrile C., 1956-1968; affiliation: Publicity News Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/52)
  - Vannini, Allan M., 1978-1981; affiliation: UM Foundation, UM Director of Development (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/53)
  - Van Slyke, 1970-1972; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/54)
  - Vaughn, Jack, 1969-1970; affiliation: Ambassador Columbia S.A., Fred Harris Campaign Director, Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/55)
  - Vaughn, Warren, 1976; affiliation: UM Foundation President (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/56)
  - Velde, Robert L. (Lt. Col.), 1962-1966; affiliation: Air Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/57)
  - Vinocur, Dr. Jacob, 1954-1962; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/58)
  - Vinyard, William C., 1968; affiliation: Botany / Yellow Bay Biological Station (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/59)
  - Vohs, John, 1966; affiliation: Oral Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/60)
  - Waddell, Betty L., ca. 1972; affiliation: Management (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/61)
  - Waddell, Thoedore J., 1968-1976; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/62)
  - Wade, Charles, 1966-1967; affiliation: Foreign Student Advisor (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/63)
  - Waldron, Ellis, 1958-1978; affiliation: Political Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/64)
  - Wallace, Robert E. Dr., 1961-1970; affiliation: Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/65)
  - Wang, Frank, 1979, 1981; affiliation: Mathematics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/66)
  - Wang, Sally A. Vogel, 1968-1972; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/67)
  - Ward, John, 1974; affiliation: Graduate Teaching Assistant Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/68)
  - Warwick, Paul S., 1967; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/69)
  - Watson, Frank J., 1955-1956; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/70)
  - Watkins, Gordon S., 1950-1970; affiliation: Scholarship Provider (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/71)
  - Waymack, William W., 1947; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/72)
  - Weddle, Richard M., 1971-1972; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/73)
  - Wedum, Arnold Dr., 1966; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/74)
  - Weigel, Eugene, 1956-1971; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/75)
  - Weisser, Jason, 1976; affiliation: CSD Group Counselor (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/76)
  - Wendt, Rudolph, 1966-1976; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/77)
  - Westbrook, Diane, 1974-1975; affiliation: Women's Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/78)
  - Weston, Donald H., 1976; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/79)
  - Wetzel, Don, 1971; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/80)
  - Wheatley, Michael, 1972, 1974; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/81)
  - Wheeler, Carolyn Leah, 1971, 1976; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/82)
  - Whicker, H.W., 1938-1939; affiliation: English, Special Collections Donor (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/83)
  - White, Elaine, 1957-1971; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/84)
  - White, Herbert M. (Hub) Mr. and Mrs., 1975; affiliation: Alumni Association Donors (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/85)
  - White, James, 1971-1972; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/86)
  - White, Dr. Philip R., 1956; affiliation: Distinguished Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/87)
  - White Roy C. Dr., 1970-1973; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/88)
  - Whited, Gary L., 1973; affiliation: Philosophy (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/89)
  - Whitehead, Robert Lowell, 1971; affiliation: Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/90)
  - Veazey, Harriet, 1974; affiliation: Manager of Missoula Red Cross (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/91)
  - Vehrs, Carson H. Jr., 1970-1973; affiliation: Director Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/92)
  - Whitwell, David Dr., 1963-1967; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/93)
  - Williams, Kim, 1976; affiliation: Center for Continuing Education and Summer Programs (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/94)